STELLA : Stories heal . Stories hurt .
If we repeat them often enough ,
they become real .
They make us who we are .
They have such power .
This I learned
on the very last autumn of our childhood .
( PSYCHEDELIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )
( TRAIN HORN BLARES )
RADIO DJ : Now it 's time to dig yourselves
out of your graves , Mill Valley .
It 's Halloween .
But be careful , ' cause when the sun goes down ,
it 's The Season of the Witch .
♪ When I look out my window
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
♪ Many sights to see
TOMMY : I did it . I 'm going to ' Nam . Yeah .
LETTERMAN : Those commies are gonna pay .
TOMMY : Let 's go scare some kiddies tonight , guys .
♪ So many different people to be
♪ That it 's strange
♪ So strange
♪ You 've got to pick up every stitch
LYNDON B. JOHNSON : ( ON TV ) But let men everywhere
know that a strong and a confident
and a vigilant America ...
Going out with your friends tonight ?
I 'd rather just stay in .
JOHNSON : ... and stand ready tonight
to defend an honored cause .
♪ ... every stitch
♪ Mmm-mmm
♪ Must be the season of the witch
CHUCK : ( ON WALKIE ) Stella , pick up .
Stella ...
I don 't want to go trick-or-treating .
Stella . Stella ,
this isn 't about candy . It 's about payback .
Get all the eggs and TP you can
and meet us at 7 : 00 .
AUGGIE : Stella , please .
This could be our last Halloween together .
CHUCK : If you think you have it hard ,
I have to fish a turd out of the toilet .
AUGGIE : You are disgusting , Chuck .
- ( BELL DINGS ) - TURNER : Hey !
You know where you 're going , kid ?
Following the harvest .
- ( BICYCLE BELL RINGS ) - BOY : Tonight only .
Mom . It 's fine .
No , it 's not .
Still a little loose in the crotch .
One more .
( SIGHS DEEPLY )
LETTERMAN 1 : Take that !
LETTERMAN 2 : Bullseye .
You got to pick up every stitch ...
Let 's go , girls .
Hey , gimme .
Eat shit , Harold .
( LETTERMEN LAUGH )
MR. MILNER : Tommy , slow down .
Must be the season of the witch
What the hell are you doing ?
A little privacy , please !
Ugh .
I said Spider-Man .
( STAMMERS ) Not a spider ...
man .
Be happy the Lord provided .
( SIGHS )
- ( GRUNTS ) - CHUCK : Mom , okay , jeez .
Mom , can I please breathe ?
Be nice .
CHUCK : Okay ! Can you please stop hugging me like that ?
Aren 't you a little old to be trick-or-treating ? Hmm ?
Aren 't you too ugly to go on a date ?
( SCOFFS ) You little turd .
- Auggie 's here , gotta run . - ( DOOR OPENS )
I don 't wanna hear it .
Thought you were gonna be Spider-Man .
Yeah , well , get used to it , okay .
I got the goods , so let 's banana split .
Stop staring at my sister ,
- you perv . - ( MUMBLES )
♪ You got to pick up every stitch
♪ The rabbit 's running in the ditch
♪ Oh , no
♪ Must be the season of the witch
( KIDS SCREAMING AND LAUGHING IN DISTANCE )
CHUCK : Hey , can you not ?
AUGGIE : I mean , these antennae aren 't even realistic .
And , if anything , a spider man
should have eight arms , not four .
Okay . At least I 'm not a clown .
For the last time , I 'm a Pierrot .
It 's a 17th-century character from la commedia dell 'arte .
Psst . Clown .
( CHUCK CHUCKLES )
Do you even know what 's in those ?
It 's the same toxic chemicals that 's giving our troops Hodgkin 's lymphoma
and curdling the breast milk of the South Vietnamese .
- CHUCK : Mmm . - And you ate them all .
Mmm .
Is that why they taste so good ?
- ( BICYCLE BELL RINGS ) - BOY 1 : Out of the way , clown .
- BOY 2 : Nerd ! - ( BOYS LAUGHING )
- ( BICYCLE BELL RINGS ) - BOY 3 : Move !
- He 's not gonna show . - What ? No , he 'll show .
Okay , Milner does it every year
and this year will be his last .
Where are you , Tommy ?
AUGGIE : I heard the school newspaper
is open to submissions again .
You should submit some of your stories .
- CHUCK : Come and steal our candy , Tommy . - No way .
- I know our school . - ( ENGINE REVS )
- ( TIRES SCREECHING ) - They would disembowel me .
( CAR ENGINE REVS )
Pontiac Catalina . It 's him , it 's him ! Okay .
Okay , just act natural .
( POP ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )
You said we 'd go out for dinner .
You and me .
How about some dessert ?
Get ready , man .
LETTERMAN : Ha-ha ! Suckers !
( LETTERMEN LAUGHING )
Oh , what 's that smell ?
- Oh , it 's old-man undies ! - Ugh !
- ( TIRES SCREECH ) - CHUCK : We got him .
All right , here we go . Let 's do this . Let 's do this !
Bully this , asshole !
Douchebags !
God damn it ! Those little shits .
( TIRES SCREECH )
And now for the poo d 'etat .
( ENGINE REVS )
Eat turd , shitbird !
- ( RUTH SCREAMS ) - TOMMY : Holy shit .
- RUTH : Stop the car ! - LETTERMAN : Put it out !
( TIRES SCREECH )
( PEOPLE CLAMORING IN DISTANCE )
What is Ruth doing here ?
Chucky , you little brat !
I don 't know . I knew she was
going on a date but not with him .
- ( SLAMS BAT ) - Damn it !
- ( CHUCK YELLING ) - I 'm gonna murder them !
- Argh ! Come back ! - ( SLAMS BAT )
( ALL PANTING )
CHUCK : Go !
TOMMY : I 'm going to get you !
Let 's get ' em !
STELLA : Come on , guys , go !
( EXCLAIMS )
TOMMY : Over there ! Get him !
CHUCK : Oh , douchebags , nine o 'clock !
( INDISTINCT CHATTER ON SCREEN )
Oh ...
MAN ON SCREEN : ... behind those tree
if you want to go check it out .
( ALL PANTING )
Go ahead . Go ahead .
STELLA : Is this seat taken ?
- Uh , I don 't ... Guess not . - ( CAR DOOR CLOSES )
Hey , get out of my car .
STELLA : Please , please .
CHUCK : Be out of here in a minute .
STELLA : Thanks , okay .
What are you guys doing ?
We 're saving our bacon .
Sorry .
CHUCK : Okay , okay . We 're good .
- AUGGIE : We 're good ? - CHUCK : He 's gone .
( PANTING )
AUGGIE : Thanks . We owe you one .
- I am a Pierrot . - ( CHUCKLES )
( SNIFFING )
- You live in here ? - BOY : Hey .
Stay out of my stuff .
CHUCK : Got it .
So , what are you doing alone at a drive-in ?
What are you still doing in my car ?
I understand you 're ...
You 're not from here , are you ?
( STAMMERS ) Where are you from ?
Forgive my friend .
He did not get enough oxygen in the womb .
More than you , clown .
Can you guys stop ?
It 's him , not me .
Yeah , we 're stopping .
Your friend is a little nosy .
- Night of the Living Dead . - ( WOMAN ON SCREEN SCREAMS )
CHUCK : It 's a good flick .
You 've seen it ?
" All right , Vince , hit him in the head ,
- " right between the eyes . " - ( CHUCKLES )
That 's the best flick all year .
BOY : Yeah , yeah , it 's ... It is .
Ramon .
Stella .
Chuck .
AUGGIE : Auggie .
( SOFT THUD )
TOMMY : ( GROGGILY ) Get out of the car .
Get out of the car .
( SIGHS )
- Get out of the car . - ( GRUNTS )
I don 't think that you heard me .
( SIGHS )
Everyone needs to get out .
- Mmm-mmm . - TOMMY : Now .
You too ,
- wetback . - ( LETTERMEN CHUCKLING )
You 're not going to try and run away
like Mommy too , now are you , Stella ?
( SNIFFING )
You smell like shit .
( SNICKERS )
Get the hell off my car .
( CAR HORNS HONKING )
MAN 1 : Hey , down in front . You 're blocking the view !
MAN 2 : Come on !
WOMAN : I can 't see the movie !
Hey ! Get back in your car or get the hell out of here !
Hey !
This ain 't over .
MANAGER : Let 's go .
MAN 2 : Move it , you idiot .
- MANAGER : Let 's go . - TOMMY : Huh ?
MANAGER : Get back in your car . Let 's go . Come on .
Okay , let 's go .
Where we goin ' ?
That way .
TOMMY : Okay , we 'll go together .
( SIGHS IN RELIEF )
You okay ?
Just excuse me for a second .
( CAR DOOR CLOSES )
Did I say something ?
No , that asshole , Tommy did .
Her mom left when she was a kid , just like that .
Yeah , people wouldn 't stop talking about it , though .
You know , we live in a small town .
Yeah , the gossip got really mean .
Jeez .
AUGGIE : Yeah , but it still bothers her ,
so I guess that stuff sort of sticks with you .
CHUCK : Yeah , and we 're like her only friends now .
So , I would say she 's definitely not your type .
It 's Stella . She 's not anyone 's type .
Don 't think I 'd agree with that .
You like every girl . It doesn 't count .
It 's not every girl .
Tell me you at least you got a switchblade .
Can I see your switchblade ?
Did I say I had a switchblade ?
( STUTTERS ) No , I guess you didn 't say you had ...
- He has a switchblade . - I know .
Well , it is Halloween , so ...
Do you want to see a haunted house ?
( SCREAMS )
RAMON : You weren 't kidding .
STELLA : Told you it wouldn 't disappoint .
RAMON : I don 't know , you 'd think on Halloween , this place would be hoppin ' .
CHUCK : Oh , it was , for a while ,
then some kid went missing , so they boarded it up .
I think it 's being torn down for a mall or something .
Hey , guys .
CHUCK : Clowns first .
- Really ? - ( CHUCK SCOFFING )
AUGGIE : Okay , there , we saw it . Can we go now ?
CHUCK : ( SCOFFS ) Who ordered the chicken ?
Because I don 't like to spend my nights in a house
- where a child murderer lived ? - ( CLUCKING )
RAMON : Someone was killed in that house ?
That 's pretty dark .
Who lived here ?
STELLA : The Bellows .
One of the first families to settle here
in the late 19th century .
CHUCK : Built the paper mill that pretty much
put this town on the map .
AUGGIE : We could at least look for some stairs .
Yep .
Just as I thought .
They got this place locked up pretty tight .
RAMON : Anyone got a pen ?
Meet Lola . She is madly in love with me .
AUGGIE : Yeah , your hand maybe .
Nice .
Lola ! Hey , what ?
( DOOR CREAKS )
( WHISPERS ) He 's so much dreamier than you .
STELLA : The Bellows had a secret :
a daughter that they never allowed to leave the house .
The myth is that there was something really off about her .
A really scary part
is that her family erased her from every single portrait .
To this day , nobody 's ever found a picture of Sarah .
They disowned her .
( SCREAMS , CHUCKLES )
- Better run , clown . - AUGGIE : Shit !
CHUCK : Better run ! ( GIGGLES )
Bet you can 't catch me !
( FOOTSTEPS RUNNING )
AUGGIE : Chuck , if you jump out at me ,
I 'm going to punch you in the throat .
RAMON : So what happened to her ?
STELLA : Kids would come from all over
in hopes to get a peek at Strange Sarah .
And though they never saw her ,
they could hear her .
Through the wall .
Sarah told them stories .
Scary stories . ( CHUCKLES )
Some kids never returned home .
Children around town died ...
Poisoned , they said .
Everyone knew it was Sarah .
But before the mob could even get their hands on her ,
she 'd already hung herself
with her own hair .
( CHUCKLES )
And as the legend goes ,
if you come to the Bellows House at dark ,
and ask Sarah to tell you a story ...
- ( STOMPS FOOT ) - ... it 'll be the last story
- you ever hear . - ( BOTH CHUCKLE )
Mwa-ha-ha-ha !
RAMON : Oh , what 's this ?
( SHELF CREAKS )
Push the other way .
Push .
( SOFTLY ) No way .
( DOOR CREAKING )
( STELLA GASPS )
( GATE CREAKING )
STELLA : Well , that 's it .
( CLICKS )
( DOOR CREAKS )
( GASPS )
Sarah 's room .
( DOOR CREAKS OPEN )
AUGGIE : You 're not going to scare me .
Chuck ?
( SNICKERS QUIETLY )
CHUCK : What the ...
( GULPS )
( SLOW FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( FLOORBOARD CREAKING )
( FAINT EERIE LAUGHTER )
( FLOORBOARD CREAKS NEAR DOOR )
( CHUCK GASPS )
What ? Where 's the old lady ?
( PANTING ) And the dog ?
AUGGIE : What old lady ?
We gotta get out of here .
Stella ! Stella ! We got to get out of here !
Stella , let 's go !
STELLA : Guys , you 've gotta see this ! Come here .
( LIGHTER CLICKS )
AUGGIE : Who ordered the chicken ?
CHUCK : Shut up .
This is where her family kept her .
Locked her away from the world .
All alone as some sort of freak .
She must have just sat right here
and told her stories to the kids through this wall .
CHUCK : How have we never seen this before ?
AUGGIE : I don 't think anyone wanted us to ?
( MUSIC BOX PLAYING GENTLE MELODY )
CHUCK : Can we get out of here now ?
( BOOK SCRAPING )
RAMON : What 's that ?
STELLA : I can 't believe it .
It 's her book of scary stories .
She had a book ?
CHUCK : There 's no book in the version of the myth I heard .
The book is a part of every version of the myth .
And ...
that it was written in children 's blood .
Well , kids died hearing these stories , okay ?
Look , let 's put it back where you found it
and let 's just get out of here now .
- ( DOOR SLAMS ) - Oh , shit !
RAMON : I got it , I got it , I got it .
Everybody , okay , everybody just shut up .
CHUCK : Oh , no . It 's the old lady and the dog !
RUTH : ( MUFFLED ) Tommy , stop it , okay ?
Just let them out .
- ( BANGS ON DOOR ) - CHUCK : ( MUFFLED ) Ruth , is that you ?
- Will you open the door ? - ( CACKLES )
Joke 's over . If you don 't open it ...
- AUGGIE : You can 't do this ! Come on ! - ... I 'll tell the Chief .
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
Why would you do that ?
AUGGIE : This isn 't funny ! Tommy , come on .
It 's my little brother .
Please .
AUGGIE : Open the damn door !
( SOFTLY ) Open it .
CHUCK : Ruth ! Down here . Let us out !
( SCREAMS )
You 're trash anyway .
CHUCK : Tommy , I 'm sorry about the burning shit , man .
I hope you find a way out .
Good ?
( PANTING ) Yeah .
- ( SCREAMS ) Get it off me ! - AUGGIE : Oh , you 're fine !
No ! Get it off , get it off me ! Get it off me !
- RAMON : Hey ! - ( DOOR RATTLING )
Get it off me ! Get it off me !
- You 're fine . I got it , I got it . It 's fine . - Something 's bit me !
RAMON : Hey , can you help me with this ?
- AUGGIE : The spiders are gone . - RUTH : Thank you .
Jesus , Auggie . Okay , you 're such a horndog .
Can you lose your stiffy for a second
and help us get out of here ?
Not funny ! There 's a lady present .
Ladies ... present .
RAMON : Come on , come on ! You gotta push harder .
- Come on . - ( CHUCK GRUNTS )
( SOFTLY ) Sarah Bellows , tell me a story .
Tell me a story .
Sarah Bellows , tell me a story .
CHUCK : Wait , wait , wait . I hear something .
Someone 's here .
- He came back . - ( DOOR BANGING )
- RUTH : Tommy ! - CHUCK : You got ...
- AUGGIE : We 're sorry , we 're real sorry . - RUTH : Thank you !
CHUCK : I ... I take back everything I ever said , man .
AUGGIE : Sorry , man !
- ( BANGING ON DOOR ) - RUTH : Tommy , please !
( DOOR LOCK CLICKS )
CHUCK : Ruth , why would you date a psychopath like that ?
RUTH : Better than fishing for turds .
AUGGIE : So , who unlocked it ?
RAMON : Who cares ? Let 's just get out of here .
- RUTH : Nice Pierrot costume . - AUGGIE : Thank you .
See ?
RAMON : Well , that was fun .
RAMON : Shit !
STELLA : I 'm really sorry about all of this .
- RAMON : Why did he do this ? - CHUCK : This is low ,
even for Tommy ,
like " farting in my milk carton
" and making me drink it " kind-of-low .
It was the fifth grade .
It was ninth .
I can try and scrounge up something to help .
I got it . It 's fine , thank you , though .
I 'll just stay here until the morning .
Get it into a shop .
We have a sofa in the basement .
You 're welcome to use it .
Hey , look , I really don 't want any trouble .
We 'll just have to be gone before Dad gets up .
( INDISTINCT TV CHATTER )
MAN ON TV : An AM / FM stereo table radio with auto ...
( DOOR CLOSES )
Sam 's pet turns out to be a sewer rat ?
You 've got some demons .
It 's not finished yet .
I used to love these as a kid . You collect them ?
Oh , I 've read every single issue .
Cover to cover .
You know , if you 're serious about being a writer ,
you can 't do it here .
You gotta move to the city .
I couldn 't leave my dad .
Uh , the , uh ...
basement is downstairs .
Yeah , that 's usually where they are .
( EXHALES )
( STELLA READS )
( WIND WHISTLES )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE )
MRS. MILNER : Tommy Milner .
It 's late ! Are you drunk again ?
It 's Halloween .
MRS. MILNER : You were supposed to deliver eggs to the Wolvertons .
Now ?
MRS. MILNER : Now !
( CHICKENS CLUCKING )
What ?
( CHICKENS SQUAWKING )
This is bullshit .
( WIND WHOOSHING )
STELLA : " Tommy hated that scarecrow all his life .
" He took the eggs and left for the last time . "
Tommy ...
( WIND WHISTLING )
Eat shit , Harold .
( KICKS )
( CROW CAWS )
( STALKS RUSTLING )
( GRUNTS )
( CREAKING )
Mom !
( GASPS )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
( GASPING )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANING )
Mom !
( CHOKING )
Help me !
Mom !
( RETCHING )
( CHOKING )
( COUGHS )
( CHOKING AND GAGGING )
( GRUNTING )
( STIFLED RETCHING )
TURNER : Oh , my God .
Will you look at this ?
I thought you were going to be on your way , stranger ?
I 'm trying .
Whew .
You know , no one 's seen this high school kid
named Tommy Milner since last night .
Witnesses say he got into a fight
at the drive-in .
Milner didn 't do this to your car ,
did he ?
I never got your name .
RAMON : Ramon .
Rodriguez .
TURNER : Look , I think it 'd be a good idea
if you stuck around for a few days .
Comprende ?
Rodriguez .
STELLA : It wasn 't there before .
The red ink was wet .
And it did feel like blood . It was thicker than ink .
AUGGIE : How could you eat that ?
Do you know how many body parts are in there ? Seven !
I read it in a magazine .
Cool . He turns into a scarecrow ?
Fresh twist .
That 's not a twist .
I told you , the story , it ...
Uh , it just appeared .
Tommy didn 't even show up to school .
It 's like he just disappeared .
Everyone knew he was eager to go shoot some commies .
Maybe he just , I don 't know , left early ?
There was that room ...
AUGGIE : Just drop it .
Nah , tell me .
In the house , when I was hiding ,
the room was old . I mean new . Perfect ,
like when they lived there , and I saw this ...
this old lady and this dog
and they were just staring at me
- with this look ... - AUGGIE : Listen to yourselves .
Nothing happened to us in that house
except for what Tommy did to us .
If he 's gone ,
good riddance .
We should never have gone there ,
we should never have taken the book .
You let a ghost story get into your heads .
That 's all it is .
- ( CROWS CAWING ) - STELLA : I 'm worried .
Tommy wasn 't at school .
His name was in the book .
I mean , there 's no way it 's actually connected , right ?
Yeah , of course it 's not .
- ( INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER ) - ( GASPS )
RAMON : Stella , I can 't get mixed up with the police .
I have to see it .
( WIND WHISTLING )
STELLA : It 's what Tommy was wearing last night .
Okay , what if this is Tommy ,
and what happens in the book
is exactly what 's happened for real ?
Stop trying to scare me .
It 's just a scarecrow .
- BOY : Did you hear about Tommy ? - GIRL : He 's missing .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
STELLA : ( SIGHS ) Here 's your book back .
( RATTLING )
You 're home late .
Picked up another shift ?
You have to ?
Can 't say no .
There 's food in the fridge .
Did you always work this much ?
Even when Mom was here ?
Heard the Milner boy didn 't come home .
Eh , everybody 's been talking about it .
Please just come straight home next few days , okay ?
Yep .
RUTH : Ow .
You got enough zit paint on there ?
It 's a spider bite , you butt-pimple .
A spider ...
- Ah , damn it , my banana ! - ( SIGHS )
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
I thought you were leaving ?
Hope you 're hungry .
Oh , I 'm starving . Thanks .
You know , I can 't stop thinking
about Tommy 's disappearance .
There has to be some ...
( GASPS SOFTLY )
Where did you get that ?
It was just here on your bookshelf .
No , I ... I was just here . It wasn 't .
I took this back to the house .
What ?
How is it getting ... How is it back here again ?
( GASPS )
- What 's happening ? - What the hell !
How does that work ?
But we 've got to make it stop !
RAMON : " A mother was digging at the edge of the garden
" when she saw a big toe . ' It looks nice and plump , '
" she said , ' I 'll put it in the stew ... ' "
What kind of story is that ?
What ...
Auggie .
Auggie !
( ON WALKIE ) Pick up !
AUGGIE : No , there 's nothing here .
( OBJECTS SHUFFLING )
I told you , I mean , the least you could have done
was go to the store before you and Jeff took off
for the weekend .
No , I 'm not gonna call him " Dad . "
Okay , I 'm eating the stew .
The stew in the fridge ?
Yeah , well someone made it .
Okay , I 'll see you when you get back . Love you .
STELLA : ( OVER WALKIE ) Auggie , pick up !
Hey , I 'm eating .
STELLA : Auggie !
Stella !
Auggie , do not eat anything .
Listen , you 're in the next story !
Whatever you do , do not eat anything !
Har-har . Very funny .
Did Chuck put you up to this ?
Auggie , this isn 't a joke .
Okay , the story is writing itself right now .
I don 't know how or why , but I 'm reading it right here .
" A sound scared him . It was a voice .
" And it called out , ' Who took my toe ? ' "
It 's a corpse looking for her missing toe .
Yeah , I know this story .
My dad used to tell me this story .
It scared me so much as a kid , but ...
Am I not supposed to wait for someone to say that
' cause I don 't hear anything .
Listen , we 're reading it right here .
" And then the voice grew louder :
" ' Who took my toe ? ' "
AUGGIE : I 'm all alone .
There 's no voice .
Yeah , well , there has to be a voice .
You 're the only one saying it .
STELLA : Auggie !
Auggie !
Oh , no , Auggie , pick up .
- Auggie , don 't eat anything . - ( CRUNCHING )
- ( GAGS ) - Auggie !
Oh , God !
RAMON : Auggie . Auggie ?
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
STELLA : Auggie ? Come on , Auggie , pick up !
( WHISPERS ) Did you hear that ?
( STAMMERS ) Hear what ? I don 't hear anything .
( WHISPERS ) There was a toe in the stew . A freaking toe .
What does the book say happens next ?
STELLA : " August got very scared .
" But he thought , ' It doesn 't know where I am .
" ' It 'll never find me ... ' "
How does the book know that ?
And then he heard the voice again ...
( EERIE VOICE ) Who ...
took ...
my ...
Toe .
( GRUNTS )
Auggie , just get out of the house !
STELLA : He 's only a couple of blocks away !
( BREATHING RAGGEDLY )
( FAINT FOOTSTEPS )
( FLOORBOARD CREAKING )
( FOOTSTEPS )
( RASPY BREATHING )
- ( GASPS ) - ( EERIE VOICE ) Who ...
took ...
my ...
toe ?
( BREATH TREMBLING )
Come on , come on .
( GASPING )
( DOORKNOB RATTLES )
( WHIMPERS QUIETLY )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( YELPS )
- ( SCREECHES ) - ( SCREAMS )
( GASPING )
( GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
STELLA : Auggie ?
Auggie !
OFFICER : Tommy ! Tommy Milner !
RADIO DJ : And as if this year
hasn 't been grim enough already ,
we have a disappearance on our hands , friends .
Our own Tommy Milner ,
right here , in little Mill Valley .
( TRAIN HORN BLARING IN DISTANCE )
STELLA : I was the one that found the book .
I took it home .
This is not your fault .
You know , ( SNIFFLES )
I caused
every single bad thing that happened in my life .
( SNIFFLING )
My mom leaving .
And now Auggie .
None of that is true .
( CAR APPROACHING )
Sorry we 're late . Ruth ran out of zit paint .
I swear , if you weren 't so stressful to deal with
in the first place , I wouldn 't have zits .
CHUCK : What 's so urgent ?
Where 's Auggie ?
Auggie 's gone .
RAMON : Another story was written .
Right in front of our eyes .
I don 't get it .
What is this ?
This is a stale joke .
Halloween 's over .
Where the hell is Auggie ?
We don 't know .
His parents are traveling , and he 's just gone .
What do you mean you don 't know ?
Okay , well , then let 's find him !
STELLA : I don 't think he 's coming back .
First ...
CHUCK : I knew something happened .
- STELLA : ... Tommy disappeared . - CHUCK : Saw that old lady ...
And then now Auggie .
They had their stories in the book ,
and it happens every night .
Jesus , he ate a toe ?
You don 't read the book .
The book reads you .
I 'm afraid that we woke something up .
That the same thing is going to happen to all of us .
We were all in that house .
No , this isn 't real , okay ?
Stories can 't hurt you .
Sarah Bellows is a myth ,
and even if she 's not , she 's dead .
We need to go to the police .
STELLA : No , we can 't .
They know what Tommy did to Ramon 's car
and they think that he had ...
Auggie ! We need to find Auggie .
Not going to the police .
They 'll never believe a word I say .
Well , then we 'll make them believe .
By the time that they make sense of everything ,
we 're all going to be dead .
CHUCK : No , no , no .
If ... If we can 't go to the police , what do we do ?
Just sit and wait for our story to be written ?
There 's gotta be some way to stop a witch .
Well , I don 't believe any of it .
I gotta go . My musical 's tonight ,
and I 'm not falling for another one
of your dumb Halloween pranks .
STELLA : It 's not a prank , Ruth .
CHUCK : Ruth , please , don 't go .
I know you want to be a writer , Stella ,
- but this prank is sick . - CHUCK : No !
CHUCK : Ruthie ! Ruthie , stop .
STELLA : Do you really think this is going to work ?
It worked in Salem .
( FIRE CRACKLING )
( YELLS ) Why ? Why won 't you burn ?
I hate you ! I hate you . I hate you . God damn it !
This is ... This is why I don 't read books !
STELLA : We know we can 't burn or destroy it ,
but how much do we actually know about Sarah Bellows ?
( STELLA SIGHS )
CHUCK : Listen to this one :
" After Sarah hung herself ,
" the Bellows family fired Sylvie Baptiste
" as she and her daughter , Lou Lou ,
" were thought to be responsible
" for teaching her black magic . "
If it 's in the paper , it has to be true , right ?
Is there a picture of Sarah ?
No , just her name .
But , uh , I did find an ad for brain salt ,
cures headaches and constipation .
Not sure why it didn 't take off .
Auggie , Auggie would have loved that .
STELLA : My eyes are literally gonna start bleeding ,
and we still have nothing on Sarah .
What year did she hang herself ?
Uh ...
1898 .
In just one year , all her family members left .
What do you expect ?
I mean , who wants to stick around with the name
that 's synonymous with murdering kids ?
Not stick around ,
I mean gone .
Like , off the face of the earth .
Take the father , Deodat .
The cat owned a paper mill
and yet he leaves it without ever selling it ?
No stories written about him ,
not even a letter , just disappears .
( SOFTLY ) Deodat ...
Deodat .
I 've seen that name .
" Deodat was a wealthy man who wanted to go hunting . "
Give me another name .
Uh ... One of their sons , Ephraim .
Ephraim Bellows .
They didn 't just leave the town .
They each have a story .
Why ?
Oh , my God .
Oh , my God , it 's happening again .
She 's writing another story .
CHUCK : " The Red Spot " ?
Why are you looking at me ?
What ?
Oh , shit ! Oh , shit , it 's me ?
It ... I 'm gonna die ?
I don 't want to die ! I even haven 't had sex yet .
" One night , a spider crawled across
" a young girl 's cheek and bit her . "
Spider ? I was the spider man ! I 'm ...
Wait , " young girl " ?
RAMON : " Went to the restroom . "
It 's not you . It 's your sister .
Ruthie ?
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
STAGE MANAGER : ( ON PA ) Performers to stage in 20 minutes .
( EXCITED CHATTER )
( GIRLS GIGGLING )
Oh , honey , you need to do something about that .
( SIGHS )
( SOFTLY ) Yeah .
( RUTH PANTING )
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( GASPING )
( MOANS )
( WHIMPERING )
( ALL PANTING )
( GIRLS GASP )
It 's a different bathroom .
- STELLA : Second floor ! - RAMON : Okay .
( GASPS )
( EERIE VOICE WHISPERS ) Ruth .
( MOANING )
( WHIMPERING )
( SCREAMS )
CHUCK : Move . Out of the way !
( GASPING )
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
( MOANS )
( GASPS )
( SCREAMING )
CHUCK : Ruth !
( RUTH SCREAMING )
Oh , my God , Ruth !
RUTH : Help me , help me ! ( SOBS )
RAMON : Ruth , I got you .
It 's okay . It 's okay . I got you .
RUTH : Help me , help me . Get them off !
Get them off ! ( SHRIEKING )
RAMON : Ruth , it 's okay . It 's okay . I got you .
- Get them off ! - RAMON : You 're going to be okay , all right ? It 's okay .
Move , move , move !
( SHRIEKS )
CHUCK : You 're okay . You 're okay , you 're okay , Ruthie .
Help ! Somebody , get help , now !
CHUCK : You 're okay , Ruthie , you 're okay .
- It 's all finished . - Get them off , get them off .
They 're all gone , Ruthie . They 're all gone .
RUTH : Get them off me . Get them off . Get them off me .
- ( SCREAMING ) Get them off me ! - Ruthie , they 're all gone ,
they 're all gone , they 're all gone , okay ?
- Get them off me . ( SOBBING ) - You 're okay .
Get them off me .
CHUCK : It 's intense . I hope she 's okay .
I saw her . Sarah was there .
She was controlling the entire thing .
My sister 's gone .
We 're next .
You find it ?
Louise Baptiste ...
Lou Lou ?
220 Goldshire Road .
( DOORBELL BUZZES )
CHUCK : I had this messed-up dream again .
I was trapped in the red room .
And there 's that fat , pale lady who keeps whispering ,
" This is an evil place .
" Run away while you still can . "
I 'm scared the witch is going to use it against me .
Hello .
Uh , does Lou Lou Baptiste live here still ?
" I don 't want to bomb anybody
" if it 's not necessary to save ... "
Tricky Dicky . That 's no name for a president .
Mama , you got company !
STELLA : Lou Lou , can you hear us ?
( KEY WINDING )
( MUSIC BOX PLAYING GENTLE MELODY )
You may be the next .
STELLA : Why do you say that ?
Why , that 's the song , girl .
♪ Don 't ever laugh as a hearse goes by
♪ For you may be
♪ The next to die ♪
Sarah loved that song .
We have her book .
LOU LOU : You found her book ? Give it here .
( MUSIC BOX STOPS PLAYING )
I give her this .
I feel so sorry for that girl ,
sitting down there in the darkness all by herself .
Did your mom ever teach her anything ?
Teach her ?
Black magic ?
( LOU LOU CHUCKLES )
LOU LOU : No .
There is no magic , child .
There is only rage .
Then how is she still writing the stories ?
Stories hurt .
Stories heal .
Do you know what you have done ?
Done what ?
You shouldn 't have taken the book .
You made her angry .
" The worms crawl in , the worms crawl out ... "
She gets this way sometimes .
Look , I need to know .
Another time . I need to settle her down .
No , we need to know . I need to know .
She told the doctors everything she knew
at the hospital where that disturbed girl hung herself .
But I ... I thought ...
Everyone always said Sarah hanged herself in the house .
CLAIRE : You weren 't there . Mama was .
( LOU LOU SINGING INDISTINCTLY )
The hospitals have records .
Records of Sarah .
Then what are we still doing here ? Let 's go .
RADIO DJ : It 's election day , folks ,
so let your voice be heard .
Say no to the war ! Say no to Vietnam .
Say no to sending our children to die .
STELLA : Excuse me .
We need to see the records of a former patient .
We don 't give out patient records .
Well , uh ,
I mean ,
she died about 100 years ago .
I 'm sure she or anybody else
probably doesn 't care , you know .
Why do you kids wanna look at old patient files for ?
Uh , for a school assignment
on , uh ...
psychological human studies .
CHUCK : Yes , the studies .
Mmm-hmm .
DOCTOR : I think they put the files
from the old hospital in the red room .
Red room ?
NURSE : Six weeks processing time .
At most .
Need a pen ?
CHUCK : So much for that .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Come on !
- No . - ( GRUNTS )
We are not going to the red room !
No , we are going to the red room .
- No , I 'm not . - Yes .
No . I 'm not doing it .
( MUTTERS )
WOMAN : ( ON PA ) Dr. Kaufmann to telephone , please .
Dr. Kaufmann .
CHUCK : I told you about my dream . I don 't want to go .
So , it isn 't actually red . You 're fine .
It is called the red room , okay ?
Who said it had to be red ?
Uh-uh . Count me out .
Okay . Just ... stay here .
Be quick . It 'll be fine .
( GROANS )
Just don 't get caught .
( ELEVATOR BELL DINGS )
( DOORKNOB RATTLES )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
ORDERLY : George Foreman .
He 's going to be the world champion in ' 73 .
Hey , you know where you 're going ?
Oh , God . Oh , God , oh , God , oh , God .
ORDERLY : Hey , you there .
You 're not supposed to be here .
Hey ! Stop !
( BOTH PANTING )
The R.E.D. room .
( SWITCH CLICKS )
RAMON : Admittance records , psychological exams ,
what she ate ...
STELLA : This is ... everything .
She was admitted by her own family .
Says here that she was suffering
from achromasia-albinism .
They put her in her basement because she was different .
Here , her supervising doctor was ...
Dr. Ephraim Bellows .
Her own brother ?
( SOFTLY ) Yeah .
Jesus ! They tortured her .
Look , electroshock ,
isolation therapy ,
lateral cerebral diathermia treatment .
What about this thing ?
What is this ?
I 've seen one of these before .
It 's a wax cylinder .
They used them to make recordings before LPs .
So , does that mean we 're going to get to hear Sarah ?
( PANTING )
ORDERLY : He went this way .
Sound the alarm !
EPHRAIM : ( ON EDIPHONE ) You 're going to tell the truth now .
Aren 't you , Sarah ?
SARAH : ( WEAKLY ) I didn 't hurt the children .
I didn 't .
Ephraim ...
EPHRAIM : That isn 't the truth , is it ?
SARAH : ( TEARFULLY ) I didn 't do it .
I didn 't hurt ...
- ( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ) - ( SARAH SCREAMING )
( CRACKLING STOPS )
EPHRAIM : Tell the truth , Sarah .
SARAH : ( SOBS ) I 'm your sister ...
EPHRAIM : You poisoned those children .
SARAH : No . No .
I tried ...
I tried to save them .
But nobody listened .
I didn 't want them hurt , but you wouldn 't let me out .
EPHRAIM : Sarah ...
- ( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ) - ( SARAH SCREAMING )
- ( CRACKLING STOPS ) - EPHRAIM : Tell the truth .
She doesn 't know what she did .
SARAH : It was the water .
EPHRAIM : We went over this , Sarah .
SARAH : ( SOBS ) The water .
EPHRAIM : There 's nothing wrong with the water .
That 's why you 're here .
SARAH : The mill .
It was the mercury from the mill .
You poisoned the wa ...
- ( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ) - ( SARAH SCREAMING )
She didn 't do it .
It was her family .
EPHRAIM : Sarah ,
are you still here ?
SARAH : ( IN EERIE TONE ) I 'll tell you .
I 'll tell you what you want to hear .
EPHRAIM : And what 's that ?
( STATIC CRACKLES )
( WAX CYLINDER SPINS MECHANICALLY )
SARAH : Charlie had a dream of a red room ...
EPHRAIM : Charlie ?
The R.E.D. room .
EPHRAIM : Charlie who ?
Chuck .
SARAH : In his dream ,
a woman with a pale face ,
black eyes ,
and long black hair
slipped silently into his room .
SARAH : ( WHISPERS ) She leaned over and whispered ,
" This is an evil place .
" Run away while you still can . "
( GASPING )
( ALARM BLARING )
( ELECTRICITY BUZZING )
( SCREAMS )
( ALARM CONTINUES BLARING )
That 's not good .
Chuck !
( ALARM CONTINUES BLARING )
CHUCK : Help !
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLES )
Help ! Somebody , help !
( ALARM CONTINUES BLARING )
( MOANING SOFTLY )
( PANTING )
Help ! Please , somebody , help .
( ALARM CONTINUES BLARING )
Help . Help !
Somebody , help !
- Come on ! - ( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
( GASPING )
( PANTING )
( WHIMPERING )
( CHUCK CONTINUES WHIMPERING )
( CHUCK WHEEZING )
( MOANS SOFTLY )
STELLA : Chuck ! Chuck , where are you ?
RAMON : Chuck !
Where is he ?
He should be right here .
Chuck ? Chuck ?
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
STELLA : Chuck .
NURSE : So ,
where 's your little friend ?
MAN : ( ON TV ) News coverage of election night ' 68 continues .
( PHONE RINGS )
Stella ?
STELLA : Dad .
Are you okay ? Where are you ?
Stella ?
( VOICE BREAKING ) I 'm afraid I 'm gonna die , Dad .
Aw , sweetie , don 't say that .
Tell me what 's wrong . Tell me what I can do .
Can 't do anything about it .
I can 't do anything about it .
No , no . You gotta help me out here , sweetie .
Tell me where you are . I will get there right away .
I don 't care what you 're going through , just tell me , please .
If I go missing ...
Missing ?
If you can 't find me ...
Find you where ?
Stella ?
I didn 't leave you .
I would never do that to you .
I don 't understand
what you 're talking about , Stella , leave me ?
Why would you leave me ?
Is someone there with you ? Do ...
Please just listen to me , sweetie .
It 's not your fault , Stella .
It 's not your fault she left .
Everyone said it was because of me .
Oh , no , please , please , please listen to me .
It 's not your fault she left .
It was never , ever about you . It was about her .
I don 't know , somewhere deep down inside , she just ...
felt trapped or something , I don 't know , I ...
It 's complicated .
I wish I had answers for you , sweetie ,
but I just don 't and I 'm so sorry .
( SNIFFLES )
I love you , Dad . I gotta go .
It 's not your fault , Stella . Please don 't hang up , sweetie .
I 'm sorry , I 'm sorry , I gotta go .
I 'm telling you , it wasn 't your ...
So ? Is your dad going to come pick you up ?
Oh , Stella , what 's going on ?
I need answers from you right now .
Understand ?
Richard Nixon is still holding at 43 and Humphrey 35 ,
but , uh , Wallace has come up one point .
What about my call ?
Rules don 't apply to draft dodgers .
You think I wouldn 't find out ?
Ramon Morales .
You 're gonna do your duty to this country
one way or the other .
I can help you if you tell us about your missing friends .
Told you everything we know .
( CHUCKLES ) Oh , yeah , right .
Sarah Bellows ' book .
The stories write themselves and it all comes alive .
We can 't find any bodies .
Yeah , I know .
It 's hard to believe .
We saved Ruth at school .
I mean , we stopped her from getting killed .
Ruth Steinberg ?
That 's who you 're talking about ?
You didn 't save anyone .
She 's stuck in the nuthouse for the rest of her life .
Get out of here , Stella . You 're free to go .
You 're so much better than this draft dodger .
Come on , what would your father say ?
I 'm not leaving .
Since you 're not going to ' Nam ,
maybe a night behind bars will loosen those lips of yours .
- Come on , Hobbs . - ( LOCK CLICKS )
Go home , dig out that 10 bucks
you 're gonna owe me when Nixon wins ,
and , uh , I 'll close up here .
HOBBS : All right , have a good night .
Nighty-night , lovebirds .
I should 've told you .
You must think I 'm a coward , but ...
I would never think that .
Two months ago they shipped my brother back from Vietnam
in pieces .
I 'm so sorry .
Last week when I got my draft notice ,
I couldn 't .
They just send you there to die .
If the book reads me ,
I 'm afraid what it 's going to say .
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
TURNER : There you go , boy .
Yeah , that 's good , huh ?
" Me Tie Dough-ty Walker " ?
( ELECTRICITY BUZZING )
Who came up with all this sick stuff ?
Is this you , Stella ?
We didn 't write the stories .
- ( THUNDER RUMBLES ) - ( ELECTRICITY CRACKLES )
( DOG WHINING )
( DOG GROWLING )
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
( LOW GROWLING )
( LOW GROWLING CONTINUES )
- Trigger ? - ( TRIGGER GROWLS )
Wait , is there another story ?
Please , you have to let us out !
Okay , if there 's another story ,
we are all gonna be in danger .
( GROWLING )
RAMON : Tell us what 's happening !
STELLA : What 's the story ?
( GROWLING IN CADENCE )
STELLA : Please just listen to me , okay ?
We 're all going to die .
( TRIGGER GROWLING IN CADENCE )
( FAINT RUSTLING )
It 's my turn .
STELLA : Okay , what happens in the story ?
Just tell me which name is in the book .
Ramon .
( THUNDER CRASHES )
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
( TRIGGER GROWLING )
It 's a campfire story .
It used to scare me to death .
( THUNDER CRASHES )
( WHIMPERS )
The Jangly Man is coming .
He 's going to take me ...
What 's going on ?
RAMON : He 's going to say it . Listen .
Me tie dough-ty walker !
Are you shitting me ?
( GASPING )
( GUN CLICKS )
( GROWLS )
( RATTLING )
Please , just let us out , please !
( BONES CRACKING )
( SNARLING )
( SNARLS )
( WHIMPERS )
JANGLY MAN : Me tie dough-ty walker !
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
( RUSTLING , SCRAPING )
( BOTH GASPING )
( GROANING )
Ramon !
Ramon .
STELLA : Oh , my God , Ramon .
- Oh , my God , what is that ? - ( GROWLING )
Help . Help , please . Can someone hear me ?
Keys .
RAMON : Hurry !
( GROWLING )
( GRUNTS )
( GRUNTING )
Coward !
STELLA : I got the keys .
Come on , come on , come on , come on .
Coward !
RAMON : Run ! Go , go , go !
( CHEERING ON TV )
What are you waiting for ?
Go to the house .
Tell her the truth .
That thing will follow me .
But the stories come true every time .
Then you better run fast .
Stop her and you 'll stop this .
( GRUNTS )
( SNARLS )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( GASPS )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
( CAR ROOF THUDDING )
( JANGLY MAN GROWLING )
- ( ENGINE REVVING ) - ( TIRES SCREECHING )
( GROWLS IN PAIN )
( JANGLY MAN GROANING )
( CAR DOOR RATTLING )
( GRUNTING AND GROWLING )
- ( BONES CRACKING ) - ( GROANS )
( BODY THUDS )
( SCREECHING )
STELLA : Sarah !
Can you hear me ?
God damn you ! You have to stop telling these stories !
We didn 't do anything to you !
We just want to help you ! We know you 're innocent !
We know you didn 't poison the kids !
( TEARFULLY ) But , please , you just have to stop telling the stories !
( CLOCK TICKING )
( YOU MAY BE NEXT PLAYS SOFTLY )
( FIRE CRACKLING )
Stella !
Where are you ?
No , no , no , no .
Stella .
( GROWLING IN DISTANCE )
( GROWLING )
Stella !
- ( FOOTSTEPS RUNNING ) - ( GASPS )
( FOOTSTEPS FADE )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
- Hey , Stella ! - ( JANGLY MAN GROWLS )
DELANIE : She 's out of her room again .
DEODAT : Boys ? Sarah 's out !
Find her now !
HAROLD : Sarah !
- ( CHANDELIER CLINKING ) - ( GROWLING )
( PANTING )
HAROLD : Sarah !
You leave that to me , Harold .
DEODAT : Sarah , where are you ?
( DOOR CLOSES )
HAROLD : Sarah !
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
GERTRUDE : I hear her .
( OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING )
( BREATH TREMBLING )
She 's here !
She 's in here !
( WHIMPERS )
( SNARLS )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( GASPING )
EPHRAIM : Sarah !
Where are you ?
STELLA : Lou Lou .
( DOOR RATTLES )
( GROANS , PANTS )
DELANIE : Did you see Sarah ?
YOUNG LOU LOU : ( PANTS ) No , ma 'am .
HAROLD : She 's lying .
DELANIE : You wouldn 't lie , Lou Lou ?
YOUNG LOU LOU : No , ma 'am .
No , I didn 't see Sarah .
No , Mr. Bellows , please , no !
Please , no !
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
You can 't hide from us .
HAROLD : Got you !
No ! No !
Help me ! Help me !
- STELLA : Help me ! - Stella !
STELLA : Please ! Help me !
- Please , help me ! - EPHRAIM : She 's been telling everyone about the water .
DELANIE : What should we do with her ?
Somebody , help me , please .
You 're going to shut your ugly mouth or we 're going to shut it for you .
Please , help me !
- ( JANGLY MAN GROWLING ) - STELLA : Help me , please !
DEODAT : Going back where you belong .
STELLA : ( SOBBING ) Help me , please .
DELANIE : Be quiet or you know what you 'll get .
Please . I 'm not Sarah . Please !
Please let me go . Please ...
Let me go .
Please , don 't put me in here .
HAROLD : Try this again and we 'll send you to the asylum .
STELLA : Please . Wait ! Please ?
DELANIE : You should have stayed in your room .
( SOBBING ) Please . Please . Please .
I didn 't do it .
- DELANIE : You don 't deserve the light . - ( SWITCH CLICKS )
No !
I 'm telling you , I 'm telling you ,
I 'm not Sarah .
Please .
( MUFFLED THUD )
( CONTINUES SOBBING )
- ( SOFT TAPPING ) - ( SOBBING STOPS )
- ( SARAH BREATHING SHAKILY ) - ( CHAIR CREAKS )
( WHIMPERING SOFTLY )
( BOOK THUDS )
( YOU MAY BE NEXT PLAYS SOFTLY )
SARAH : ( WHISPERS ) Stella ...
( GASPS )
I have another story
just for you .
( SNARLING )
Stella ,
if you can hear me , wherever you are ,
tell her the truth .
No .
It 's time that you hear a story , Sarah .
You were a victim .
Now you 've turned into a monster .
The one that they said you were .
Stella .
You took my friends .
Two of the people that I love most .
( PANTING )
Ramon !
( GROWLS )
RAMON : ( MUFFLED ) Stella !
( BREATH TREMBLING )
Are you going to take him , too ?
What your family did to you ,
what they said , that 's on them .
But what you do ,
this is on you , Sarah .
It 's all on you .
( WHIMPERS SOFTLY )
I 'll tell your story .
The real story , I 'll tell the truth .
But the rage ,
the rage has to stop , Sarah .
( GASPS )
Use your blood .
( STELLA GRUNTS )
Sarah Bellows was innocent .
She knew the truth ,
and tried to stop them .
She was brave .
She was harmed and destroyed
by her own family .
By their greed ,
and their lies
and their sins .
I 'll tell your story .
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
You can let it go .
You can let it go , Sarah .
( SHRIEKING LOUDLY )
( GROWLS )
( GASPING )
( RUMBLING )
( RUMBLING STOPS )
( WHIMPERING )
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( EXHALES SHARPLY )
STELLA : Stories hurt .
Stories heal .
If we repeat them often enough ,
they become real .
They have that power .
They make us who we are .
RAMON : Stella .
STELLA : I 'm just so happy you 're okay .
STELLA : And if there 's anything I learned from Sarah ,
it 's to never give up .
( TYPEWRITER DINGS )
I told Sarah 's story exactly as I promised .
I wrote about the pale , lonely girl
who wrote stories in the dark .
And how she was turned into a monster by her family .
Some people believed me . Most didn 't .
Because , like Sarah ,
I was a lonely girl
who knew how to tell a good creepy story .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Write me ?
Every day .
See you around .
ARMY OFFICER : What 's your name , kid ?
RAMON : Ramon Morales .
STELLA : Stories can teach us to care .
They make us brave enough
to admit that we need each other .
Give us a home to go back to .
( SNIFFLES )
Chuck and Auggie are still gone ,
but I know there is a way to bring them back
and that the secret is in the book .
And we won 't stop ...
until we find them .
PLAYING LANA DEL REY : Season Of The Witch
SKDS @ BBSR